[{"question":"which object is smaller?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The bamboo cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The redunknown cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"What is the material of the medium cube?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"Dirt"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"Wood"}],"answer":1},{"question":"How many cubes there?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"3"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"4"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which object has lower density?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The large redunknown cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The small bamboo cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Is the small bamboo cube heavier than the large RedUnknown cube?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which object has lower friction?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The large redunknown cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The small bamboo cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which object has lower restitution?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The medium wood cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The large redunknown cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which quadrant will the medium wood cube be in when it finally stops moving ?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"\u2160"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"\u2161"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"\u2162"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"\u2163"}],"answer":2},{"question":"Which quadrant will the large RedUnknown cube be in when it finally stops moving ?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"\u2160"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"\u2161"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"\u2162"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"\u2163"}],"answer":3},{"question":"Which object will stop moving earlier?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The medium wood cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The small bamboo cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which object will stop moving first?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The medium wood cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The large redunknown cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will the medium wood cube travel to quadrant \u2160?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Will there a collision in the quadrant \u2163?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"How many collisions will happen between objects?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"<=3"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":">3"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will the small bamboo cube collide more than once?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will the large RedUnknown cube collide with the wall in this video?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will the medium wood cube collide with the small bamboo cube in this video?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which objects is the first collision?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The medium wood cube and the large redunknown cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The large redunknown cube and the small bamboo cube"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"The medium wood cube and the small bamboo cube"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"The small bamboo cube and the wall"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which objects is the last collision?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The small bamboo cube and the wall"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The small bamboo cube and the medium wood cube"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"The small bamboo cube and the large redunknown cube"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"The wall and the large redunknown cube"}],"answer":3},{"question":"Will the large RedUnknown cube collide with other objects after it stops moving?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":1}]